And by clicking Generate, and need professional headshots, yes, thank you.
For now, we just want to continue with these three options. I click Generate All.
And we'll wait again. Get your headshots. Nope. Thank you.
Generate selected.
So as you see, it's generating the headshot results for me.
And as you see, these are my generated headshots, right?
So it has to be, you know, all of these situations, whatever.
So that's pretty much all that we get from AI headshot tool for tour.
And if I come back, so by clicking on each, as you see, we'll be able to open them up,
and we'll be able to download each, like download any of them that we want, right?
And this is pretty much all that we have with this tool as well.
So I come back to the homepage of the tour.